The legends of horror have returned!
Puppet Master: Axis of Evil is a horror, fantasy,
war film directed by David DeCoteau.
Following the murder of Andre Toulon by Nazi assassins during the height of World War II, a young Danny Coogan finds his
crate of mysterious puppets, and discovers their plan to attack a secret American manufacturing plant.
Danny Coogan, played by Levi Fiehler.
Beth, played by Jenna Gallaher.
Don, played by Taylor M. Graham.
Ben / Max, played by Tom Sandoval.
Uncle Len, played by Jerry Hoffman.
Mr. Gifford, played by Mike Brooks.
Puppet Master: Axis of Evil (also known as Puppet Master 9: Axis of Evil) is a 2010 American action horror film
directed by David DeCoteau, it is the ninth official entry into the Puppet Master series of horror films.
and the first in the Axis trilogy.
The film explores themes of japan, world war ii,
ninja, killer doll, evil puppet.
The tone is dark.